{
    "subject": "resource/Devil_May_Cry_3:_Dante's_Awakening",
    "predicate": "property/mc",
    "object": "84",
    "human_readable": "The Metacritic score of Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening is 84.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9638259410858154,
            "question": "What is the Metacritic score for Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9197097420692444,
            "question": "Based on its Metacritic score, how would you describe the overall reception of Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8698875904083252,
            "question": "How does the Metacritic score for Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening compare to other entries in the series?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8407742977142334,
            "question": "Are there any other games with similar Metacritic scores to Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7952660918235779,
            "question": "What can a high Metacritic score tell you about the potential enjoyment of a video game like Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6369064450263977,
            "question": "Is Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening considered a critically acclaimed game?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5799918174743652,
            "question": "How well-received was Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening by critics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.548724353313446,
            "question": "What does a Metacritic score of 84 indicate about a video game?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2169913351535797,
            "question": "What factors contribute to a high Metacritic score for a video game?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21209202706813812,
            "question": "What are some common themes or elements found in highly-rated action games like Devil May Cry 3?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Metacritic score of Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening is 84.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4175_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What factors contribute to a high Metacritic score for a video game?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4175_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does a Metacritic score of 84 indicate about a video game?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4175_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How well-received was Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening by critics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4175_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4175_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4175_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4175_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4175_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4175_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4175_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4175_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4175_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4175_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4175_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states that the Metascore for Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening is 78, not 84.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, the Metacritic score for Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening is actually 78, not 84. Therefore, the statement that the Metacritic score of Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening is 84 is incorrect."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The Metacritic score of Devil May Cry 3: Dante's Awakening mentioned in the context information for point 3 does not match with the one from point 2.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}